Guide to the Hill Family Papers, 1662-1994 (bulk 1835-1970)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Albert Levitt, 1906-1968
  - Subseries H. Writings
    - A Protestant Defends the Roman Church, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 1411)
    - An Open Letter from Albert Levitt to Chester Merrow, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 1412)
    - Autobiography (incomplete), undated (Box 25, Folder 1413)
    - Book review, The Salem Witch Trials, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 1414)
    - Campaign issues, prohibition, address at Stamford Baptist Church, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 1415)
    - Central Law Journal, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 1416)
    - Collected letters to editor; The Connecticut Citizen; Camp Deans Thanksgiving Program, 1917-1927 (Box 26, Folder 1417)
    - Collected writings, legal, undated (Box 26, Folder 1418)
    - Discipline and Moarle, lecture, 1918 (Box 26, Folders 1419-1423)
    - Four Stone Faces, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 1424)
    - How to Study Law, dedicated to Elsie Hill Levitt, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 1425)
    - Jesus, Judas & John, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 1426)
    - Judas Iscariot, An Imaginative Autobiography, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 1427)
    - Lectures, essays, statements, 1922-1968 (Box 26, Folder 1428)
    - Legal briefs, Sufficiency of the Declaration, undated (Box 26, Folder 1429)
    - Lists, books and articles written by Albert Levitt, 1925-1932 (Box 26, Folder 1430)
    - Love and the Law, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 1431)
    - Our Constitution, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 1432)
    - Outline of a book on legal problems, "You and the Law,", undated (Box 26, Folder 1433)
    - Poetry, 1924-1925 (Box 26, Folder 1434)
    - Speech, Convention of the Independent Republican Party, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 1435)
    - Speech, delivered to the Tax Payers Association of Norwich, CT, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 1436)
    - Speech, The Study of Law, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 1437)
    - Taxpayers Are People Too, undated (Box 26, Folder 1438)
    - Ten Years in Connecticut, undated (Box 26, Folder 1439)
    - The Chaplain and Army Morale, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 1440)
    - The Churchman Journal; published essays, letters to editor, 1963-1965 (Box 26, Folder 1441)
    - The Conflict Between Vaticanism and Americanism, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 1442)
    - The Law Behind the News, undated (Box 26, Folder 1443)
    - The Law of Community Property in California, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 1444)
    - The Lieutenant or the Colonel, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 1445)
    - The Political Faith of an American Lawyer, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 1446)
    - The President and the International Affairs of the United States, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 1447)
    - The Young Democrats and the Future, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 1448)
    - Thesis, Meadville Theological School, The Categories of Activity and Growth Applied to the Idea of God, undated (Box 26, Folder 1449)
    - Thomas Jefferson & Pope John XXIII, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1450)
    - To Elsie Hill Levitt from Her Father on Her 17th Birthday, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 1451)
    - Vaticanism, Political Principles of the Roman Catholic Church, NY: Vantage Press, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 1452)
    - Was Clyde Griffiths Guilty of Murder in the First Degree?, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 1453)
    - Who Owns Connecticut, The Nation, Vol. CXXXVIII, No. 3591, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 1454)
- Series III. Clara Hill, 1836-1967
  - Subseries A. Biographical
    - Address books, 1934-1953 (Box 26, Folder 1455)
    - Army diary of Moses Asbury Hill, 1862 (Box 26, Folder 1456)
    - Birth certificate, 1871 (Box 26, Folder 1457)
    - Church missionary accreditation, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 1458)
    - Citizenship registration papers, 1907-1929 (Box 26, Folder 1459)
    - Deeds from Albert Levitt, Elbert Miller, Helena Hill Weed, 1923-1927 (Box 26, Folder 1460)
    - Diary, 1910-1914 (Box 26, Folder 1461)
    - Diary text re: "games Mexican children play,", 1924 (Box 26, Folder 1462)
    - Genealogy, descent form George Hill, undated (Box 26, Folder 1463)
    - Genealogy, descent form Gov. John Webster & Lieut. Samuel Smith, undated (Box 26, Folder 1464)
    - Genealogy, descent from Governor Tristram Coffin, undated (Box 26, Folder 1465)
    - Genealogy, descent from Thomas Wilder, undated (Box 26, Folder 1466)
    - Genealogy, descent from William Westwood, undated (Box 26, Folder 1467)
    - Genealogy, English countries, Scotland and Ireland/Clara M. Hill genealogical research, undated (Box 27, Folders 1468-1472)
    - Genealogy, epitaphs, circa 1910-1919 (Box 27, Folder 1473)
    - Genealogy, index cards (incl. data re Barlow, John), undated; (formerly Boxes 165-166) (Boxes 37-38)
    - Genealogy, lines of descent of Clara M. Hill, undated (Box 27, Folder 1474)
    - Genealogy, manuscript notes, undated (Box 27, Folder 1475)
    - Genealogy, maternal and paternal lines of descent, undated (Box 27, Folder 1476)
    - Genealogy, notes, circa 1930-1939 (Box 27, Folder 1477)
    - Genealogy, notes re Hill Family, undated (Box 27, Folder 1478)
    - Genealogy, passengers of the Mayflower, undated (Box 27, Folder 1479)
    - Genealogy, Rice Family, undated (Box 27, Folder 1480)
    - Genealogy, Ward, Andrew, undated (Box 27, Folder 1481)
    - General, biographical documents, [circa 1940-1959] (Box 27, Folder 1482)
    - Letters of introduction, 1900-1931 (Box 27, Folder 1483)
    - Medical records, 1927-1932 (Box 27, Folder 1484)
    - Passport, US, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 1485)
    - Scrapbook, Vassar College, 1890-1895; (formerly Box 198) (Box 49)
    - Scrapbook/"Nonsense Book," limericks, poems, notes, undated (Box 27, Folders 1486-1491)
    - Visa, Mexican, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 1492)
  - Subseries B. Correspondence
    - ERA, InterAmerican Commission of Women, 1931-1934 (Box 27, Folder 1493)
    - ERA, to/from legislators/Clara Hill, 1951-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1494)
    - Family correspondence, 1910-1954 (Box 27, Folders 1495-1499)
    - General correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1500)
    - Hill, Elsie to Clara Hill, 1910-1949 (Box 27, Folder 1501)
    - InterAmerican Commission of Women, 1932-1933 (Box 27, Folder 1502)
    - InterAmerican Commission of Women, undated (Box 27, Folders 1503-1504)
    - Legislators to Clara Hill, with her notes; ERA, letters sent to NWP headquarters, 1953 (Box 27, Folders 1505-1506)
    - Levitt, Albert to Clara Hill, undated (Box 27, Folder 1507)
    - Personal correspondence, 1899-1955 (Box 28, Folders 1508-1521)
    - Socci, Luisa to Clara Hill, 1932-1954 (Box 28, Folders 1522-1526)
  - Subseries C. Ephemera
    - Business cards and printing plate, undated (Box 28, Folder 1527)
    - Invitation, cards, check for "good behavior" at Vassar, 1892 (Box 28, Folder 1528)
    - Suffrage banner and pin, undated (Box 28, Folder 1529)
    - Tags, 1903-1915 (Box 28, Folder 1530)
  - , Subseries D. Financial and Legal
    - Check register books, 1950 -1955 (Box 28, Folders 1531-1533)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1930 (Box 28, Folder 1534)
    - Correspondence, EJ Hill's German government bonds, mixed claims, 1928-1937 (Box 28, Folder 1535)
    - Court papers, Clara Mossman Hill vs. Norwalk Hospital Association, 1954-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1536)
    - Court papers, Clara Mossman Hill vs. The Employers Group Insurance Co., 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1537)
    - Invoices, deeds, 1836-1929 (Box 27, Folder 1538)
    - Invoices; agreement - National Bank of Norwalk, includes will codicil, 1919-1955 (Box 27, Folder 1539)
  - Subseries E. Manuscripts
    - A Valentine to you, dear Joe (poem), undated (Box 28, Folder 1540)
    - Christ of the Indian Road, by E. Jones (notes by Clara M. Hill), undated (Box 28, Folder 1541)
    - Christian Science: What Is It, by Rev. Wm. Short (notes by Clara M. Hill), undated (Box 28, Folder 1542)
    - Church History, assignment sheet, undated (Box 28, Folder 1543)
    - Church History, notes, undated (Box 28, Folder 1544)
    - El Dia de las Muertas, Mexico, undated (Box 28, Folder 1545)
    - El Hijo de Dios (Son of God), undated (Box 28, Folder 1546)
    - El percado, el perdon, el castigo, undated (Box 28, Folder 1547)
    - Emily Post, undated (Box 28, Folder 1548)
    - Escuela Biblica de Vacaciones en Pueblo Nuevo, undated (Box 28, Folder 1549)
    - Glimpses at Eastern District, undated (Box 28, Folder 1550)
    - Hardshell Baptist Sermon, undated (Box 28, Folder 1551)
    - Land question, undated (Box 28, Folder 1552)
    - Latin American History, notes, undated (Box 28, Folder 1553)
    - Latin American literature, undated (Box 28, Folder 1554)
    - Looking Outward (missionary to Mexico), undated (Box 28, Folder 1555)
    - Los dos primos, Barnabi y Marcos, undated (Box 28, Folder 1556)
    - Mohammedanism, undated (Box 28, Folder 1557)
    - Noah Webster, undated (Box 28, Folder 1558)
    - Notes on customs in Mexico, undated (Box 28, Folder 1559)
    - Oaxaca Churches, undated (Box 28, Folder 1560)
    - Opinions on misc. topics, undated (Box 28, Folder 1561)
    - Oppenheim, Phillips bibliography, undated (Box 28, Folder 1562)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 28, Folder 1563)
    - Religion, "The Life of God in the Soul of Man,", undated (Box 28, Folder 1564)
    - Savonarola, la Antorcha de Florencia, undated (Box 28, Folder 1565)
    - Speeches, presented to church groups, undated (Box 28, Folder 1566)
    - The King's Business, undated (Box 28, Folder 1567)
    - Virtue Its Own Reward, undated (Box 28, Folder 1568)
    - Work of Foreign Missions, undated (Box 28, Folder 1569)
    - Written assignment, Ed. 468, undated (Box 28, Folder 1570)
  - Subseries F. Clippings
    - Connecticut history, 1939-1943 (Box 27, Folder 1571)
    - Detective fiction, murder mysteries, 1931-1946 (Box 27, Folder 1572)
    - Ebenezer Hill, 1903-1914 (Box 27, Folder 1573)
    - Ebenezer Hill, obituaries, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 1574)
    - Education, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 1575)
    - Elena Hill Weed, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 1576)
    - Genealogy, 1904 (Box 27, Folder 1577)
    - Hill and Mosman families, 1919-1940 (Box 27, Folder 1578)
    - Hill, Clara, 1930-1955 (Box 27, Folder 1579)
    - History, politics, 1914-1950 (Box 27, Folder 1580)
    - Latin America, 1921-1935 (Box 27, Folder 1581)
    - Leslie Levitt Latham, 1947-1955 (Box 27, Folder 1582)
    - Literary, 1933-1951 (Box 27, Folder 1583)
    - Literary reviews, 1933-1950 (Box 27, Folder 1584)
    - Miscellaneous, 1913-1949 (Box 27, Folder 1585)
    - Religion, 1907-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1586)
    - Science, Technology, 1936-1952 (Box 27, Folder 1587)
    - Women, 1922-1948 (Box 27, Folder 1588)
  - Subseries G. Printed Material
    - Connecticut history, 1935-1951 (Box 29, Folder 1589)
    - Genealogy, undated (Box 29, Folder 1590)
    - Letterhead, stationery, undated (Box 29, Folder 1591)
    - Pamphlets, booklets, handbills, sheet music, religious publications (incl. Mexican), suffragette publications, political and educational materials, book jackets, 1895-1967 (Box 29, Folders 1592-1604)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 29, Folder 1605)
  - Subseries H. Subject Files
    - Answers to magazine contests, undated (Box 29, Folder 1606)
    - Bible study teaching syllabus; teaching materials, 1924-1925 (Box 29, Folders 1607-1616)
    - Bible study teaching syllabus; teaching materials, 1924-1925 (Box 30, Folders 1617-1636)
    - China, missionary school, undated (Box 30, Folder 1637)
    - Historical notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 1638)
    - Lecture notes - The Preparation for the Middle Ages, undated (Box 30, Folder 1639)
    - Lists, undated (Box 30, Folder 1640)
    - Mexico, broadsides, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 1641)
    - Mexico, mission schools, journal notes, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 1642)
    - Philosophy and Literature, notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 1643)
    - Recipes, undated (Box 30, Folder 1644)
    - Spanish vocabulary notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 1645)
    - The New Deal, Susan B. Anthony, undated (Box 30, Folder 1646)
    - U.N. charter, ms excerpt, undated (Box 30, Folder 1647)
- Series IV. Ebenezer Hill, 1800-1919
  - Subseries A. Correspondence
    - General correspondence files, arranged alphabetically, by Ebenezer Hill, 1906 (Box 30, Folders 1648-1652)
    - To and from Ebenezer Hill (includes handwritten note from Samuel L. Clemens, May 1908), 1904-1908 (Box 31, Folder 1661)
    - Reverend Moses Hill (letters to Moses Hill), 1855 (Box 31, Folder 1663)
    - Legal and business, includes contracts, articles of incorporation, 1892-1908 (Box 31, Folder 1662)
    - Letters of introduction, 1901 (Box 30, Folder 1654)
    - Political, 1902-1909 (Box 30, Folder 1655)
    - President McKinley, William, 1900 (Box 30, Folder 1656)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1901-1910 (Box 30, Folder 1657)
    - President Taft, William Howard, 1908-1916 (Box 30, Folders 1658-1659)
    - President Wilson, Woodrow, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 1660)
  - Subseries B. Biographical and Travel
    - Diaries, 1890-1896 (Box 32, Folder 1664)
    - Diaries, 1897-1899 (Box 32, Folder 1665)
    - Diaries, 1900 (Box 32, Folder 1666)
    - Diaries, 1903-1904 (Box 32, Folder 1667)
    - Diaries, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 1668)
    - Diaries, 1907 (Box 32, Folder 1669)
    - Diaries, 1909, 1914 (Box 32, Folder 1670)
    - Diaries, Miscellaneous pages, undated (Box 32, Folder 1670A)
    - Financial ledger, undated (Box 32, Folder 1670B)
    - Political notes and clippings, 1906-1909 (Box 32, Folder 1671)
    - Political notes and clippings, 1910-1912 (Box 32, Folder 1671A)
    - Political notes and clippings, 1913-1915 (Box 32, Folder 1671B)
    - Political notes and clippings, 1913-1917 (Box 32, Folder 1671C)
    - Political notes and clippings, undated (Box 32, Folder 1671D)
    - Diary - trips around the world, Siberia, Philippines, England, France, Germany, Panama, Egypt, Palestine, Mexico, 1895-1909 (Box 32, Folders 1672-1673)
    - Diary, trip to Germany, study of denatured alcohol, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 1674)
    - Scrapbook, bills introduced by Hon. Ebenezer J. Hill, 1907 (Box 34, Folder 1700)
    - Scrapbook, political press clippings, 1896 (Box 34, Folder 1701)
    - Scrapbook, political, 1897-1900; (formerly Box 198) (Box 42)
    - Scrapbook, political, 1901-1904; (formerly Box 199) (Box 43)
    - Scrapbook, political, 1904-1907; (formerly Box 198) (Box 49)
    - Scrapbook, political, 1907-1910; (formerly Box 199) (Box 44)
    - Scrapbook, political, 1908-1909; (formerly Box 199) (Box 45)
    - Scrapbook, political, 1910-1912; (formerly Box 200) (Box 46)
    - Scrapbook, political, 1912-1914; (formerly Box 200) (Box 47)
    - Scrapbook, political, 1914-1917; (formerly Box 200) (Box 48)
    - List of books once held in the library of Ebenezer Hill, undated (Box 34, Folder 1702)
    - Travel documents, invoices, 1904-1905 (Box 34, Folder 1703)
  - Subseries C. Printed Material
    - Invitations/announcements - Calling Cards, 1900-1906 (Box 32, Folder 1675)
    - Invitations/announcements - Colonial Dames, D.A.R., invitations to Mary Ellen Hill, 1905-1916 (Box 32, Folder 1676)
    - Invitations/announcements - Commemorations, memorials, dedications, dinners, including McKinley inaugural materials, 1800-1909 (Box 33, Folders 1677-1678)
    - Invitations/announcements - Diplomatic, 1912-1917 (Box 33, Folder 1679)
    - Invitations/announcements - General, 1899-1916 (Box 33, Folder 1680)
    - Invitations/announcements - Taft, Presidential tour to Philippines & Japan, programs, itineraries, ephemera, seating charts, postcards, menus, 1905-1906 (Box 33, Folders 1681-1688)
    - Invitations/announcements - Weddings, incl. Aldrich-Rockefeller, Chase-Taft, Pres. Wilson, Roosevelt-Longworth, 1856-1917 (Box 33, Folder 1689)
    - Invitations/announcements - White House, 1897-1903 (Box 33, Folder 1690)
    - Invitations/announcements - White House, 1904-1917 (Box 34, Folders 1691-1692)
    - Letterhead, undated (Box 34, Folder 1693)
    - Memorial addresses on life and character of Ebenezer Hill, 1919; (2 copies) (Box 34, Folder 1694)
    - Press clippings, including account of the assassination of President Lincoln, New Haven Journal, 1865-1917 (Box 34, Folders 1695-1698)
    - Press clippings, including account of the assassination of President Lincoln, New Haven Journal, 1865-1917 (Box 31, Folder 1699)
  - Subseries D. Writings
    - A Tribute to the Memory of Senator Orville Platt, undated (Box 34, Folder 1704)
    - A Trip Through Siberia, The National Geographic Magazine, 1902 (Box 34, Folder 1705)
    - Government by Consent of the Governed, 1915 (Box 34, Folder 1706)
    - Industrial Future of New England; speech, Republican State Convention, 1907-1910 (Box 34, Folder 1707)
    - Philippine Islands, speech synopsis, undated (Box 34, Folder 1708)
    - Republican Record & Achievement, ms draft, 1907 (Box 34, Folders 1709-1710)
    - Tariff, Wages & Living, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 1711)
    - The Gold Standard Imperiled, undated (Box 34, Folder 1712)
    - The Tariff/The Philippines/"as a son of the neighboring town of Redding...,", 1904; (3 typescripts) (Box 34, Folder 1713)
    - Untitled (New Milford, Bridgewater, CT), undated (Box 34, Folder 1714)
- Series V. Mary Mosman Hill, 1835-1952
  - Subseries A. Correspondence
    - Elsie Hill to Mary Mosman Hill, 1900-1916 (Box 34, Folders 1715-1720)
    - Letters to Mary Mosman Hill, 1890-1913 (Box 34, Folder 1721)
    - Letters from Mary Mosman Hill to children, includes letters from Clara Hill to Elsie Hill, 1899-1907 (Box 35, Folders 1722-1723)
  - , Subseries B. Biographical
    - Certificates - Israel Putman Community Campground Commission, 1913-1915 (Box 31, Folder 1724)
    - Diaries, Congressional Directories, 1897-1931 (Box 31, Folder 1725)
    - Diaries, Investments and Income, 1929-1952 (Box 31, Folder 1726)
    - Diaries, Norwalk Women's Club, European travels, 1838-1898 (Box 31, Folder 1727)
    - Emily R. Mosman, poem, 1839 (Box 31, Folder 1728)
    - Genealogy index cards, undated; (formerly Box 206) (Box 39)
    - Musical programs, itineraries, 1894-1908 (Box 31, Folder 1729)
    - Photographs, Italy, Sicily, 1907-1908 (Box 31, Folder 1730)
    - Press clippings, 1894-1918 (Box 31, Folder 1731)
  - Subseries C. Subject Files
    - Composition Book, Hartford High school, incl. Amherst map, 1835-1852 (Box 31, Folder 1732)
    - Explanation of curiosities in possession of Mrs. E.J. Hill, Norwalk, CT, undated (Box 31, Folder 1733)
    - Taft Inaugural, printed material, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 1734)
  - Subseries D. Writings
    - An Old Connecticut Town, 1893 (Box 31, Folder 1735)
    - Europe's Changing Balance of Power, undated (Box 31, Folder 1736)
    - The Woman's Club, Norwalk, CT, undated (Box 31, Folder 1737)
- Series VI. Leslie Hill-Levitt Latham, 1927-1971
  - Subseries A. Biographical
    - School records and associated correspondence (Gunston Hall, Walnut Hill, Vassar), 1928-1942 (Box 35, Folder 1738)
  - Subseries B. Correspondence
    - General, 1941-1971 (Box 35, Folder 1739)
    - From Hill, Elsie M., 1952-1956 (Box 35, Folder 1740)
    - From Leslie Hill Levitt Latham, 1939-1942 (Box 35, Folder 1741)
    - From Levitt, Albert, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 1742)
  - Subseries C. Printed Material
    - Poetry Magazine, God's Dark Bedtime Verses, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 1743)
    - Programs, InterAmerican Conference, includes notes re Albert Levitt, 1936-1940 (Box 35, Folder 1744)
  - Subseries D. Subject Files
    - Teaching materials, 1927-1945 (Box 35, Folder 1745)
  - Subseries E. Writings
    - Poetry, circa 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 1746)
- Series VII. Mixed Family Material, 1711-1970
  - Subseries A. Photographs
    - Alice Paul, [circa 1914?] - 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1046)
    - Suffrage (individuals), undated (Box 36, Folder 1047)
    - Suffrage (groups), undated (Box 36, Folder 1048)
    - World Woman's Party and League of Nations, 1931-1939 (Box 36, Folder 1049)
    - U.N. – related, 1951-1961, undated (Box 36, Folder 1050)
    - Elsie M. Hill, 1900-1969, undated (Box 36, Folder 1051)
    - Clara and Helena Hill, 1890-1933, undated (Box 36, Folder 1052-1052A)
    - Elsie Hill-Levitt, 1925-1938 (Box 36, Folder 1053)
    - Elsie Hill Levitt, 1926 (Box 36, Folder 1053A)
    - Albert Levitt, 1914-1958 (Box 36, Folder 1054)
    - Albert Levitt, 1914-1926 (Box 36, Folders 1065-1065A)
    - Ebenezer Hill, includes picture book of proposed Panama Pacific International Exposition, 1915 (Box 36, Folders 1055-1055A)
    - Ebenezer Hill, undated (Box 36, Folder 1055B)
    - Mary Mosman Hill, undated (Box 35, Folder 1770)
    - Clara Hill, Mexico travels (includes negatives and prints), undated (Box 35, Folders 1766-1768)
    - Miscellaneous Hill family members, 1936-1970 (Box 36, Folder 1056)
    - Miscellaneous Hill family members, 1903-1915 (Box 35, Folder 1769)
    - Miscellaneous people and places, undated (Box 36, Folder 1056A)
    - The Rock Lot [home of Elsie Hill], 1921-1923 (Box 36, Folder 1057)
    - Trip taken by Elsie Hill to Bras d'Or Lake, Cape Breton Island, 1905 (Box 36, Folder 1058)
    - Trip taken by Elsie Hill to Sierra Mountains with Cary Fink, 1915 (Box 36, Folder 1059)
    - Flight taken by Elsie Hill from New York to Moscow, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1060)
    - Elsie Hill at Vassar College, circa 1906 (Box 36, Folder 1061)
    - Elsie Hill's walking club of Rome, 1907-1908 (Box 36, Folder 1062)
    - Joel Barlow – related, undated (Box 36, Folder 1063)
    - Lockwood - Matthews Mansion and family cemetery plot, undated (Box 36, Folder 1064)
  - Subseries B. Miscellaneous
    - Hill, Elsie, audio tapes, cassettes, reel to reel, 1964, 1968, 1970; (9 items, formerly Box 211) (Box 50)
    - Hill, Elsie, record album, 33 1/3, Elsie Hill, Women and the US Constitution, 1951 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 1753)
    - Hill, Frederick, letter of credit, copy of letter to President McKinley, 1898-1909 (Box 31, Folder 1747)
    - Hill, Helena, correspondence to/from, 1907 (Box 31, Folder 1748)
    - Hill, Moses, Sermon drafts, circa 1820-1839 (Box 31, Folders 1749-1750)
    - Hill, Moses US citizenship certification, correspondence, 1866-1890 (Box 31, Folder 1751)
    - How, Mosman Marriage Certificates, Mosman, Rice Death Certificates, 1711-1886 (Box 31, Folder 1752)
    - "The Soul of the Bible,", 1914 (Box 35, Folder 1779)
    - Dearing, John Vinton, "My Galahad of the Trenches,", 1918 (Box 35, Folder 1780)
    - Guthrie, Charles John, "John Knox and John Knox's House,", 1905 (Box 35, Folder 1781)
    - Irwin, Inez Haynes, "The Story of the Women's Party,", 1921 (Box 35, Folder 1782)
    - "Problems and Quiz on Criminal Law,", 1894 (Box 35, Folder 1783)
    - Artifacts/Ephemera, items from Ebenezer Hill's 1905 Presidential (Taft) tour to Philippines and Japan. Checkered silk sashes, embroidery, Pacific Mail Steamship Co. picture book, (formerly Box 213) (Box 52 (Oversize))
    - Artifacts/Ephemera, items from Ebenezer Hill's 1905 Presidential (Taft) tour to Philippines & Japan. Kimono, hand fans (5), Japanese & US flags, embroidery, (formerly Box 214) (Box 53 (Oversize))
    - Artifacts/Ephemera, items from Ebenezer Hill's 1905 Presidential (Taft) tour to Philippines & Japan. Embroidered box containing small lacquer boxes, (formerly Box 215) (Box 51)
- Series VIII. Miscellaneous Materials, 1662-circa 1923
  - Postcard Collection [collected by Elsie Hill?]: Cards from: Belgium, California, Colorado, Connecticut, England, Florida, France, Italy, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, South Carolina, Washington, D. C., Yosemite National Park, and miscellaneous, undated; (formerly Box 115) (Box 40)
  - Road Maps - Canada, undated (Box 35, Folder 1771)
  - Road Maps - Connecticut, undated (Box 35, Folder 1772)
  - Road Maps - Europe, undated (Box 35, Folder 1773)
  - Road Maps - Massachusetts, undated (Box 35, Folder 1774)
  - Road Maps - New England, undated (Box 35, Folder 1775)
  - Road Maps - New York, undated (Box 35, Folder 1776)
  - Road Maps - United States, undated (Box 35, Folder 1777)
  - Road Maps - Virginia, undated (Box 35, Folder 1778)